airfoiltools.com 2017-12-15

# Airfoil Tools

This privacy policy tells you how we use information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you accept the practices described here. 

This policy may change from time to time by updating this page. You should always check this page to ensure that you are happy with any changes. 

## Information collected

If you use the contact form you will submit your name and email address. This will be used to respond to your request. 

You can visit the site anonymously but Google Analytics may record information about your browser. A record your vist may be made in web server logs including the IP address of your browser. 

## Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored on your browser. Cookies are used to persist data between multiple pages, for example when you add multipe items to a shopping cart before finally going to the check out. 

At the start of each session a banner should appear at the top of the page notifying you that this site uses cookies. If you continue to use the site you have given implied consent that you will accept cookies. The table below describes the cookies used on this site. 

If you do not want to accept cookies then you can. 

  1. Refuse to accept cookies in your browser. How this can be done will depend on the browser. You will be able to use the site but a lot of the functionality won't work.
  2. Leave the site by closing your browser page.

Cookie name | Use | Details  
---|---|---  
  
PHPSESSID

| 

AirfoilTools.com

| This cookie is used to persist data in the PHP session between pages on this site. It is used to share SVG drawing information over multiple pages (e.g. plotter and full screen image), collect airfoils in the comparison application and store your airfoils. If your browser refuses to accept cookies these application will not work correctly.   
  
_utma  
_utmb  
_utmc  
_utmz

| 

Google Analytics

| These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use the site. The information is used to compile reports and to help improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where vistors have come to the site from and the pages they visited.   

This site also uses 3rd part advertising delivered by Google Adsense. The cookies used by Google, the options to disable them and privacy policy for Google advertising can be found here. 

## External links

This privacy policy only applies to the web site AirfoilTools.com. If you follow any links to external sites this privacy policy will not apply. Look at the privacy policy on each individual site to determine how they treat your data.
